I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
-I'm thinking of quitting this life.
-Is it because of a woman?
Yeah, well...
Tanaka-kun! Tanaka-kun!
（女子生徒）田中(たなか)君 田中君！
（コユキ）あっ えーと…
Uhh...
Page 31.
（田辺(たなべ)）31ページだぞ フッ
（コユキ）あ… サンキュー
Thanks.
"Classical Japanese"
"The color of the flowers
of the twin sal trees
（コユキ）
“沙羅双樹(さらそうじゅ)の花の色—”
"Classical Japanese"
is a manifestation of the saying,
"All that prosper must decline."
“盛者必衰(じょうしゃひっすい)の 理(ことわり)をあらわす…”
"Classical Japanese"
Good for you, Tanaka!
（教師）さすがだ 田中
However, this is your English period.
しかし… 今は英語の時間だ
（教師）はーい 静かにー！
Quiet down!
（田辺）やるな！
ハァ…
（コユキ）いつまで
こんな毎日が続くんだろう…
How long is this life going to continue?
At the age of 14,
my life was at a dead end.
俺の人生は 14歳にして
袋小路の中にあった
そうだ—
That is...until I met him.
あの人に 会うまでは…
"Live 1: The View at Fourteen"
（アナウンス）
生徒会からの連絡です
"Live 1: The View at Fourteen"
This is a message from
your Student Council.
The equipment used by the
various clubs should be stored-
最近 部活に使用した備品の…
The equipment used by the
various clubs should be stored-
Tanabe, did you read that article?
（コユキ）田辺もアレ読んだ？
ああ すごいよなー
大リーグで首位打者だもんなー
Yeah. Isn't that something?
The first batter up,
and in the major league, too!
（コユキ）だよなー
Yeah...
The way our lives have been,
ハァ こんな毎日じゃ—
we'll never be able to write
an interesting autobiography.
俺たち面白い自伝なんか
書けないよね
Hey, Tanaka...
おい 田中～
お前 自伝書くために生きてんの？
Are you living your life
to write an autobiography?
Of course not. But...
（コユキ）そんなわけじゃ
ないけどさ… でもさ…
Let's enjoy life! C'mon!
楽しい人生 送ろーぜ！ ほらっ
（コユキ）えっ？ おい 田辺～っ
Hey, Tanabe!
（女子部員１）
もー 吉田(よしだ)君ったら！
-C'mon, Yoshida-kun!
-Have you gained weight, Kazuko?
（女子部員２）
和子(かずこ) ちょっと太ったんじゃない？
Listen, I shortened my
100-meter time by two seconds!
（男子部員）俺 100メートルの
タイムさ ２秒も縮めちったよー
I found this great shaved ice shop.
Why don't we go?
（女子部員３）私 おいしい
アイスの店 見つけたんだ
（女子部員４）キャーッ
かけないでよね！
Don't splash me!
今度 行かない？
（女子部員４）キャーッ
かけないでよね！
へへへへっ…
おー いいねっ これっ
Oh, this is great!
This is good! It's good! It's good!
いいよ いいよ いいよ！
お～っ！
Oh! It's Ishiguro-sempai!
石黒(いしぐろ)先輩だ！
（コユキ）えっ…
（田辺）ビューティーフェイスに
ダイナマイトボディー
A beautiful face and dynamite body!
スポーツ万能なうえに
成績も常にトップ10(テン)！
A great athlete and her grades
are always in the top ten!
Izumi Ishiguro's the perfect
Miss Higashi Middle School!
完璧なミス東(ひがし)中 石黒 泉(いずみ)！
She gets me hot all over! I can't stand it!
ハッとしてグッとくんね～
たまんねぇ～
-You're next!
-Okay!
Okay...I'm gonna snap away...
（田辺）
よーし 撮りまくって…
I'll sell 'em all and make me a fortune!
売りまくって ひと財産作るぞっ
おほほ～ ほほほほっ
お… おっ？
Hey! What are you doing?!
お～い 何だよ お前
I see. You want to take some too?
Is that it?
そっか お前も撮りたいんだよな
そーなんだよな ハハハッ…
Back then, Izumi-chain was
the first person to talk to me.
（コユキ）あの時—
初めて声をかけてくれたのは
泉ちゃんだった…
"Thank you for your years of patronage.
Nakajima Calligraphy School"
"Tenant Wanted"
-Izumi-chan...
-Give it back!
（コユキ）“泉ちゃん”
３年前までは そう呼んでいたんだ
（田辺）返せよー
Until three years ago,
that's what I called her.
（コユキ）“泉ちゃん”
３年前までは そう呼んでいたんだ
（女子部員）
ああっ！ 誰かいるー！
Someone's over there!
See?! There are two guys over there!
（女子部員）
ほら あそこに男子が２人！
Who are they?! 7th graders?!
（男子部員）
誰だ おい！ １年なのか？
Somebody you know, Izumi?
泉の知り合い？
-They had a camera, those two.
-Catch them!
カメラ持ってたわよ あの２人
（男子部員）
よーし 捕まえろ！
（泉）コユキ…
Koyuki?
（コユキ）ハァ… ハァ…
いやー バッチリ見られちゃったな
俺たち…
Man, they got a good look at us.
Come on. Let's go to the game center.
さっ ゲーセン行くぞ！
田中～ 早く来いよー
Hurry up, Tanaka!
（女子高生）
フフッ フフフ… やだ もう！
Hey, stop that!
Get lost!
（女の子）ウザい
（男の子１）よし いくぞ こうだ！
（男の子２）あ～
Yeah, that's it! Go!
（田辺）おっ サンキュー
Thanks!
Did it! The Golden Bat!
（田辺）よーし！
ゴールデンバットだぜ！
-Wanna eat a beef bowl?
-I'll pass. I'm broke.
（田辺）牛丼 食ってく？
（コユキ）俺パス 金ないし
I see. See ya!
（田辺）そっか じゃーな
This place seems a little iffy...
何か… ヤバそう…
ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…
Whaddya want?!
（男性）んだぁっ こらぁ！
（コユキ）うわーっ う… いってぇ
Ouch...
あ…
（男性）ヒヒヒヒヒッ… おらっ
Oww...
（コユキ）いっつつつつ～…
ハァ… 俺…
Man...
What am I doing?
何してんだろ…
Oww!
いっつ… いいっ…
（子ども１）逃がすなー！
Yay! Now it's my turn! Hold him!
（子ども２）
そっちだ そっちだ 捕まえろ！
You can't get away from us!
（子ども３）
どこ行ったってムダなんだよ
Wait!
Damn!
What's with that dog?!
何だ？ あの犬…
Hey, what are you doing?
Quit tormenting the dog!
お おい 何してんだ？
やめろよ いじめるのは
（子ども１）うっせーな！
みんな 行こうぜ！
Aw, shut up! Let's get outta here!
Yeah!
（子ども２）おう！
（子ども３）んっ
（竜介(りゅうすけ)）ベック！ カムヒア！
Beck! Come here!
I told you, you shouldn't go out alone.
You...You made me worried.
That guy's...a foreigner?
（コユキ）外国… の… 人？
（竜介）ハッハ～
気持ち悪いだろ この犬
Doesn't this dog look weird?
No, no...Not bad dog...
（コユキ）ノーノー！ ノーバット
ドッグ… え… 日本人？
Huh? You're Japanese?
（竜介）
ありがとう ベック助けてくれて
Thanks for saving Beck.
（コユキ）あ… ワンちゃん
おいでー ワンちゃん
Doggy...Come here, doggy.
Good boy...
よーし よーし…
うっ！ うわあっ！
Uh-uh. You shouldn't put your hand out
to a frightened dog.
んっんっ おびえてる犬の前に
いきなり手を出すのはダメだ
-Use these.
-Thanks.
（竜介）使いな
（コユキ）あっ ありがとう
See ya.
じゃあな
"Onochin Loans"
(This is a pack of tissues)
これ 今度お返ししまーす！
I'll return this to you next time!
Is that for real?
（田辺）それ実話？
（コユキ）うん
Yeah. First I get punched,
and then I get bitten...What a day!
殴られるわ かまれるわで
さんざんだったよ
マジかよ ひでーな そりゃ
No way...That's awful!
That weird dog...I hope
it doesn't have rabies.
あの変な犬
狂犬病 大丈夫かな
Hey! There's someone here
to see you, Tanaka!
（男子生徒）
おーい！ 田中に お客さん…
（女子生徒）石黒先輩だ！
It's Ishiguro-sempai!
Uhh...Don't let them bother you.
（コユキ）何か… 気にしないで
Listen, are you free on Saturday, Koyuki?
（泉）あのさー
コユキって 土曜空いてる？
Huh?!
What happened? You get into a fight?
どうしたの？ ケンカ？
It's nothing. I'm perfectly fine now.
大丈夫… もう全然平気
Listen, Koyuki...
あのさ コユキ…
There was another boy
with the same name as me,
（コユキ）書道教室には
同姓同名の田中幸雄君がいた
Yukio Tanaka, in our calligraphy class.
So Izumi-chan gave me
the nickname Koyuki.
(Ko - little)
そこで泉ちゃんが
俺をコユキと命名した
だから泉ちゃんは
俺をコユキって呼ぶんだ
That's why she calls me Koyuki.
"Koyuki"
I'm going bowling with some friends.
Won't you come with us?
友達と
ボウリングやるんだけどさ—
コユキも来ない？
（コユキ）うん
Yeah...
よかったー これで人数確保
Oh, good. Now we have enough people.
It's almost exam time, so it's
hard getting everyone to join in.
試験近いから みんな なかなか
参加してくれないんだもん
I didn't want to waste
the coupon Kayo-chan gave me.
せっかくカヨちゃんから
もらった券 ムダにしたくないんだ
Koyuki...Thanks.
コユキ ありがと！
（コユキ）うん！
Yeah...
Oh, I have P.E. Next. See you Saturday!
あっ 私 次 体育なんだ
じゃあ 土曜に！
I can't believe it...
信じられない…
本当にな
You're telling me...
-You seem to be happy.
-Yeah, well...
（コユキの母）
あら 何か楽しそうね
（コユキ）あ… ちょっと…
-Don't stay out too late, now!
-I won't.
（コユキの母）
あんまり遅くならないのよ
（コユキ）はーい
The uptown-bound train
will be pulling in to track two.
（アナウンス）間もなく
２番線に上り列車が参ります
Please wait behind the yellow line.
危ないですから
黄色い線まで お下がりください
黄色い線まで お下がりください！
Wait behind the yellow line!
Yay! I got a strike!
イェーイ！ ストライクだぜっ！
ウフッ
（先輩１）ナイス！ 泉ちゃん
Nice, Izumi-chan!
（先輩２）
もう！ 勝負にならないわよ
We'll never win at this rate!
Come on, Izumi. Let's switch teams.
ねえ 泉～ チーム変えない？
Koyuki...
（泉）コユキ！
手前の印を狙って投げてみな
Try aiming at those marks in front of you.
（コユキ）えいっ！
Yay! Alright!
イェイ！ よーし！
Pretty good advice, don't you think?
どうだ 私のアドバイス！
Oh, no. It's me...My talent.
いやいや 才能 才能！
Yay!
（コユキ）イェーイ！
（泉）へぇー コユキ やるじゃん！
You're pretty good, Koyuki!
（先輩３）おっしゃー
-Yes!
-Good job!
（先輩１）やるぅ
At that moment, the two years
we hadn't seen each other...
（コユキ）その時 俺たちの
２年間のブランクは—
...vanished completely.
完全に消えていた
Boy, am I hungry!
（先輩１）あー 腹減ったー
-Let's go to McDonald's!
-How about Mr. Donut?
（先輩２）ねぇ マック行こうよ
（先輩３）ミスドも よくない？
I'd rather have a Yoshinoya beef bowl.
（コユキ）あ 俺… 吉牛(よしぎゅう)
-Huh?!
What do I want?
（泉）私は何がいいかなー
I'll go by myself...
（コユキ）
俺… 別行動ってことで…
Oh! Kayo-chan!
あっ！ カヨちゃん！
Kayo-chan!
カヨちゃーん！
（カヨ）ん？ おー 泉っち！
Oh, Izumichi!
Yeah!
イェーイ
What are you doing?
何してんのさ
We're trying to decide whether
to go to McDonald's or Yoshinoya.
（泉）これからマックか吉牛
行こうかなーって
McDonald's!
マック！
I'm not hungry. Let's go somewhere else.
おなか すいてないし
別んとこ行こうぜ フッ
Kayo-chan, you're reeking of alcohol...
（泉）カヨちゃん 酒臭い！
（カヨ）ハハハ…
（女性１）アレ いいらしいよ
-I hear it's pretty good.
-No way...
（男性１）マジかよ
（男性２）ヒヒヒ…
Oh, come on...
（女性２）やーねぇ
（先輩３）
ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…
ハァ…
（泉）イェイ！
Yay!
（カヨ）フーッ しょっと…
（コユキ）うう… うあっ
飲んでるかー コユキ君！
Are you drinking, Koyuki-kun?
Yes. I'm on my second glass
of oolong tea.
はい！ ウ… ウーロン茶
２杯目突入です
ん… みんなでカラオケ行くか？
Shall we all go for karaoke?
I'll pass. I've never been to a
karaoke place, and I'm out of money.
あー 俺パス
カラオケ行ったことないし
金もないし…
（カヨ）ふーん
But Izumichi was raving
about your singing...
泉っちがコユキ君の歌
褒めてたんだけどなー
Here you go! It's on the house, kids!
（ミッちゃん）
ほらっ 若者たちにサービスだ
Oh, Mit-chan...Did you
have a chef's license?
（カヨ）あれ？ ミッちゃん
調理師免許 持ってた？
（ミッちゃん）ねーよ そんなん
'Course not.
-What's Mit-chan-san's real name?
-Why?
ミッちゃんさんって
名前 何ていうんですか？
んー 何で？
I want to thank him,
お礼 言いたいんですけど—
but I don't think a kid like me
should be calling him Mit-chan...
中坊の俺が“ミッちゃん”って
呼ぶのは… ちょっと…
Why, I don't mind you calling me Mit-chan.
なーに ミッちゃんで
かまわないよっ ヘヘッ
Thanks for the food, Mit-chan-san!
ご ごちそうさまです
ミッちゃんさん！
You know, we have a lot of regulars,
ここはな 常連さんも多いけど
誰が何やってるかなんて知らない
but none of them knows
what the others do.
They don't even know if their names
are real or just nicknames.
本当の名前なのか
あだ名なのかも知らない
そういうもんを持ち込まないのが
「レメディ」なんだ ん？
It's Remedy's policy not
to bring problems in here.
（女性）うぇ～ん！ それって
私を捨てるってことじゃん！
But that means you're breaking up with me!
As I said, I don't have the time.
（竜介）だから言ってるだろ
時間がねえんだ
Oh, man...
困ったな…
（女性）
うぇ～ん！ 竜介のバカ～
Damn you, Ryusuke...
He's called Ryusuke. Mature for 16.
あいつはリュースケって呼ばれてる
マセた16歳だ
-You know him?
-Uhh...no...
知り合いか？
え… いえ…
He's the worst...Making girls cry,
not paying back money he owes...
とにかくサイテー 女は泣かせる
借りた金は返さない
No way...
（コユキ）そんな…
（ミッちゃん）
でも 何ていうか こう…
But, how can I put it?
He has a strange attraction
for other people, that Ryusuke.
人をひきつける不思議な魅力が
あるんだよなー
竜介のヤツは…
（カヨ）んー それにさぁ あいつ
何かとハッタリが多いんだよ
-Besides, he's always bluffing.
-Mit-chan, sake!
（男性）
ミッちゃーん 酒～
（ミッちゃん）おう
（コユキ）ハッタリ？
Bluffing?
（カヨ）コユキは
「ダイブリ」って知ってる？
Koyuki, have you heard of Dying Breed?
There's this super popular band
called Dying Breed in America.
アメリカで めっちゃ売れてる—
ダイイング・ブリードっていう
バンドがあんだけどさー
What about Dying Breed? I love them!
ダイブリが どうしたの？
私 大好き！
He says he used to play in a band
with Eddy, Dying Breed's guitarist.
あいつ ダイブリのギター弾いてる
エディと昔—
バンドやってたって言うんだぜ
Who are you talking about?
ねぇ それって誰？
You idiot...
（女性）バカーッ うう…
Come on. You've got
other guys besides me.
（竜介）なんだよ お前
俺以外にも男いるだろ？
Ryusuke! Which is more important
to you?! Me or the band?!
（女性）竜介は 私とバンドと
どっちが大切なのさ！
The band.
バンド
Mit-chan-san...Would you give this to him?
（コユキ）ミッちゃんさん
これ あの人に渡してください
（ミッちゃん）おう
Sure...
Wasn't it like a drama back there?
（泉）
さっきの… ドラマみたいだったね
（コユキ）うん 何かすごかった
Yeah. It was really something.
Hey!
（先輩１）おーい！ おい おーい！
Hey! Hey! Come look at this!
見て見て
いやー よくここまでやるよなー
Somebody really did a job on this car.
It's gonna cost a mint to fix it.
これ直すの 結構かかるぜ
（コユキ）あ 先輩
あんまり近づかないほうが…
Sempai, I don't think
you should get too close.
What is it? Killjoy.
何だよー 気分壊すなぁ
Hey! What the fuck are
you doing to my car?!
（外国人１：英語）
〈おい！ お前ら俺たちの愛車に
何してんだ!?〉
（外国人２）ブハァッ
Whatsa matter, you fuckers around
here speak English, or what?
（外国人２：英語）
〈お前ら 英語 話せんのか？〉
Oh...I'm...sorry...
あ あ アイムソーリー…
Sempai! Why are you apologizing?!
（コユキ）
先輩 何で謝るんですか！
W-well...
（先輩１）いや だって…
（先輩１）うわっ
（泉たち）キャーッ
ん？ 帰るのか？
-You leaving?
-Yeah...
A young kid asked me to give this to you.
（ミッちゃん）これ 小僧が
お前に渡してくれってさ
俺に？
To me? Thanks, Mit-chan.
サンクス ミッちゃん
Fuckin' stupid little kids!
〈ふざけたガキどもだ！
ちゃんと弁償してもらうぞ〉
I'm gonna make you pay
for all of this right now!
No, no. We are not guilty. We-
（泉）ノーノー
ウィアー ノット ギルティー
ウィ ドント…
（外国人２）チッチッチッ…
What are you, a rapper or a singer?
"We are the world?!"
I'll kick your ass if you don't pay!
I'm serious. Shut the...
〈おい ちゃんと聞いてるのか？
金ださないと ひっぱたくぜ！〉
〈このガキどもが！〉
...fuck up!
Back off, damn you!
いいかげんにしろ！ このヤロー！
（泉）コユキ…
Koyuki...
Don't act big just because
you're overgrown, dumbass (baka yaro)!
体がデカいからって威張るな
バカヤロー！
Ba...ka?
〈バカ？〉
Nobody calls me baka around here!
（外国人２）
〈このイカれたガキめ！〉
You little shit! I'm kicking
your fucking ass, man! Right about now!
Stop it!
（竜介：英語）〈やめろ！〉
I saw your car two hours ago
and it was already scratched.
（竜介）
〈そいつらは犯人じゃない〉
〈２時間前に見た時には
もう傷ついてたぜ〉
Who the hell are you?!
（外国人２）〈誰だ 貴様？〉
You should apologize to these kids.
〈お前らは
この子たちに謝るべきだ〉
What the fuck?!
（外国人３：英語）
〈うるせーぞ この野郎！〉
〈謝るべきだ〉
Apologize.
Apologize!
〈あやまれ！〉
（外国人２）フンッ ハッ！
The police are right there.
〈ポリスが来るぜ！〉
Shut the fuck up, kid!
（外国人２）〈うるせー！〉
Here, let's get somewhere else.
（竜介）〈場所を移そうぜ〉
（竜介）カモン
Come on!
（外国人３）
〈ついて来い だとよ〉
Come on, he says...
竜介君！
Ryusuke-kun!
Never mind me. Get on home.
いいから早く帰れ
"Noodles"
Here are your ramen noodles.
（店員）
へいっ ラーメンお待ちっ！
（先輩３）おっ うまそーっ
"Noodles"
This looks good!
しかし さっきのポテト
あれ超まずかったよねー
But those French fries...
Weren't they just awful?
You haven't finished your ramen.
ラーメン まだ残ってるぞ
Yeah...But I really want
to eat a beef bowl!
うん でもさ… 俺 どうしても
牛皿が食べたくなったんだ
Koyuki...
コユキ…
Hey, hey-hey hey!
I-It's cool, man. It's cool.
Put that thing down, man, please.
（外国人２）〈落ち着けよ！
クールにやろうぜ〉
Put it down. Take it easy.
Please...
Well...Wanna try?
（竜介）〈おい 試してみるか！〉
〈お前の町じゃ
どうか知らんが—〉
I don't know about your town,
but my friends in New York died.
〈俺がいたＮＹじゃ
死んだ友達も少なくない〉
You can't fuck around in my neighborhood.
〈ココじゃ好き勝手させないぜ！〉
Get the fuck outta here! Fucking bastard!
〈ココから消えちまえ！〉
（外国人２）
〈撃つな 撃たないでくれよ〉
-No! No! Leave it!
-Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
（コユキ）ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…
Ryusuke-kun!
竜介君！
Damn...Treating me like trash...
ちくしょう
人をゴミ扱いしやがって…
ああ… シット！
Shit!
（コユキ）ハァ… ハァ…
竜介君！ 大丈夫？
R-Ryusuke-kun! Are you all right?!
They were so drunk, I didn't
think they'd figure it out.
あいつら 相当酔ってたから
バレないと思ったんだけどな…
Man...it hurts...
あ～… いてー
I was impressed.
俺 感動したんだ… うっ
You're such a shorty, but you
went after those big foreigners.
お前 小さいのに あんなデカい
外人に向かっていくんだもんな
ん？ どうした？
What's the matter?
Hey, hey...I'm the one
who should be crying.
おいおい
泣きたいのは むしろ俺だぜ
I'm sorry. But lately...
for a long time, actually,
（コユキ）ごめん…
でも 最近… ていうか
もうずっと前から—
I felt like no one cared if I lived or not.
いてもいなくても…
誰も俺のことなんか…
Koyuki!
（泉）コユキー！
It's them...
あ… みんな…
Hey, you guys-
皆さん…
（泉）ケガ… 大丈夫？
-Are you all right?
-I'm just scratched up.
（竜介）ああ こんなん かすり傷だ
The other day, he saved my dog.
この前
彼に犬を助けてもらったんでね
（泉）犬… ですか
Your dog?
Beck is a dog Eddy and I found
when we were in a band together.
（竜介）
ベックは 俺がエディと—
バンドを組んでたころに
見つけた犬でね
-Oh, so that's a true story?
-Oh, sorry Koyuki-kun.
（泉）わー その話って
本当なんですねー
（先輩３）
いやー すまん コユキ君
-Sorry I'm so late.
-Yeah...
（先輩３）遅れて すまん
I love the Dying Breed!
私 ダイブリ大好きなんです
Oh? Then why don't you come
and see our band sometime?
ふーん じゃあ今度
俺たちのバンド見に来なよ
Yes! I will! That's so exciting!
はい 行きます！ わあ 楽しみ！
Matt of Dying Breed is really funny.
ダイブリのマットって
面白れぇんだぜ
If he doesn't have a drink before
a show he can't get up on the stage.
いつもライブの前にさぁ—
酒飲まねえと
ステージ上がれねぇんだぜ
That looks pretty weird to me.
（田辺）ヤバいんじゃない？ それ
Now I'm pretty worried...
for Ishiguro-sempai.
俺… かなり心配んなってきた
石黒先輩の身が
I don't give a damn about you, though.
ま！ お前は どーでもいいけどな
So cheer up...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
（泉）ごめーん 待たせて！
This is Ryusuke-kun's address...
竜介君とこ この住所…
Okay...Shall we barge in on him?
よーし 押しかけちゃうか！
Huh? Right now?
え？ いきなり？
あっ ああ…
Koyuki...What kind of music
do you listen to?
（泉）コユキって
どんな音楽 聞いてるの？
（コユキ）んー… 国吉(くによし)ちえみ
-Chiemi Kuniyoshi.
-Kuniyoshi? Oh, that idol singer?
（泉）くによし？
あっ あのアイドルの子？
Yeah...I'm sure she's going
to break out soon.
（コユキ）うん！ 将来
絶対ブレイク間違いなしだと思う
（泉）ふーん…
I think it's this way.
（泉）何か こっちみたいよ
Maybe...
（コユキ）あ… そーかも
（コユキ）そして俺たちは
さんざん迷った末に—
And, after taking a lot of wrong turns,
we finally arrived at Ryusuke-kun's home.
竜介君の家に たどりついたんだ
（泉）キャッ
（コユキ）うわ…
"Fishing"
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Rock, you see, is the
vibration of the soul. Hm?
（千葉(ちば)）
ロックってのはな こう—
心のバイブレーション！
なわけよ うん
"Next Episode"
Rock, you see, is the
vibration of the soul. Hm?
"Next Episode"